Oh!!!
It bounces back!
It's gonna bounce back.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
It's nice when you can forget about the car, isn't it?
Everyday life.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Suzuka Tomita from Hinatazaka46.
What a surprise today!
I'd like to wash my car.
Yay!
So today...
Yes!
It's a private car wash booth for rent.
I came to a place where I can wash my car by hand.
I've always wanted to wash cars by hand.
I came to this place today.
It's been six months since I bought and delivered my Jimny Sierra.
It's been six months since I bought and delivered my Jimmy Sierra.
Actually, I haven't washed the car once since I bought it.
It is very dirty.
So today I would like to wash the car with your help.
I'd like to wash the car.
I look forward to working with you today.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to go home today with a shiny Jimmy Cira.
I'll do my best.
I've decided on a name for this Jimny Sheila of mine.
It's Tomitasu Suzuka.
Suzuker.
It's pronounced like this, so please remember it.
Now, can you really see it?
Is it a butt?
But it's super hard to the touch.
I thought it would be smooth and silky.
But it's really hard.
I don't want to show you how dirty it is.
Let's see.
I really don't want this to ruin the comment section.
It's so dirty!
I'm a little sad that I'm showing my dirty face here.
If there was something else, you'd probably say...
It's the dirt.
It's like this, isn't it?
I'd like to make it sparkling clean now.
Today it's brake dust, today it's brake dust.
Brake dust.
The car doesn't brake.
So level it.
Heads.
Remove and
In such a case
First from the centre.
Pan and
Clockwise.
That's already OK early First from the centre, pan and then clockwise.
That's already OK.
Yes, that's fast. Very fast.
That's why it's my favourite product.
Here we go.
Get clean.
Ooh.
Heh.
I'm learning a lot.
I'm getting to know the car as I'm washing it like this.
It's fun, it's really like cooking, just like cooking.
I'll have a look. Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
The juice is purple. It's a stain.
It's purple.
It's gonna be purple. - It's gonna be purple.
Put some foam on it.
From the top.
Bounce off.
Then we'll go down
Kouka
Ooh.
I knew it.
Oh really?
It's so purple!
Wow.
OK, we're done.
It's pretty dirty.
First of all, you've just had a lot of the undercarriage cleaned off, and now you've got to flush it down.
We'll start with this high pressure.
Undercarriage.
This one, too, from the top, from the top, and then this high-pressure one on the undercarriage.
Put this on from the top.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
It looks like this.
Wow, it's shiny.
It's totally different.
Here we go.
There's mud and stones here, too.
Yeah, you're right, it needs a wash.
Now we're going to get into the body.
We're going to spray water from the roof.
There you go! Is it done?
It's perfect.
Now we just have to spray it with water.
That's right.
What's that?
The dirt.
Okay, so we've got it down to a minimum.
Now it's time to actually lather it up and get it off.
Scrubbing.
Yes, sir.
This is the foam.
This is what you wash your body with.
Yes, sir.
What's this one called?
Mouton.
Mouton?
Like this.
Oh, still...
Marshmallow.
I'm gonna go wash.
Here we go.
Oh, that feels good.
Oh, gently.
Do you have a knack for that?
Stroke it gently.
You don't even have to look this high up.
You should also do this corner properly.
That's a lot of work.
Gently, gently, gently.
Oh, my God!
Wow.
Oh, is this what it looks like?
Is this what I think it is?
Next, the bonnet.
Yes, sir.
When you're about halfway there...
Put some foam on it again.
That's it.
Surprisingly, the foam is definitely gone.
Is it right?
It's fine.
I want to do it again.
It's a bit short.
The front part might be difficult.
Special grille.
The front is also quite easy to connect.
The front part is the most vulnerable.
Also, insects can get on it.
It's quite difficult in the back.
Yes, because of the tyres.
It might be a bit difficult.
It's better to work inside, even in the corners.
As much as possible.
It's a bit difficult in a large area.
How far did I go?
Clean up the parts you can't see.
That's right.
You have to.
It's important.
It's important to be beautiful inside and out, even if you can't see it.
That's what makes us beautiful.
Do this one, too?
And there, too.
Yes.
It's kind of mindless, isn't it, but this is really...
Yes, it is.
You could play a car.
It's nice to forget about the car, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Everyday life.
Tomorrow, actually.
I'm driving this car on the circuit.
We're going to drive this car on the circuit in Saitama.
I'm going to drive this car.
I'm going to drive on the circuit.
I'm done.
Yes, and then I'll wash it off.
I'll wash it off.
Like this. Oh, did we do this up there? Yes, I did.
Now you dry it off and wipe off the oil.
That's it.
I think that's about it.
I told you I like cars with bumps and dents, so it's probably harder to wash a car like this.
There are so many grooves.
Water keeps coming out, no matter how hard I try.
It's amazing.
It's deep.
There's a little water on the sides.
Just there.
If you don't wipe it off properly, it'll turn into water stains, won't it?
Yes, and dirt tends to accumulate there, too.
So if you don't wash the car, or if you don't wipe it down, there's moss growing on it.
Moss? Does moss grow on cars?
Yes, it does.
I can't believe it. That's funny.
Oh, it's so clean.
It looks fine.
Okay, well, I've just finished washing the car.
Take a closer look.
I'd like to show you all how clean it is.
I'd like to show you all.
Ta-da!
Look at it, look at it, look at it.
Oh, no!
It's a reflection of my face from below.
Oh, my God, you're so beautiful.
What do you think? Look at Umm's face, too.
What?
She's amazingly beautiful.
What do you think? And here, too, even though there was a lot of stuff on it earlier.
Surprisingly, it's very difficult to get to these uneven areas.
It's hard to get the water out, surprisingly.
And also in places like this, it's surprisingly hard to get the water out.
So this is the end of my Tamitasuzu car wash, it's like a new car.
It's as clean as when I took delivery of it.
Yay!
It's the first time I washed my car by hand today.
I found that there was a lot more dirt in the smallest places than I expected.
I was very puzzled by the fact that I couldn't see it.
It took a lot of time and effort.
It was a great learning day.
I'm going to wash the car a lot more from now on.
I want to keep my Jimmy Scherer shiny all the time!
Next time, I'd like to change the tyres and the front grille.
I'd like to change the front grille and other parts.
I'd like to share my customisation work with you all.
I hope you will continue to enjoy my videos and my car life!
If you liked this video, please click the like button and subscribe to my channel.
If you liked this video, please like it and subscribe to my channel!
This is Suzuka Tomita.
See you in the car!